Your drink, sir.
Are you in possession
of the diamonds?
Affirmative.
Congratulations, John.
Thanks to you,
we've recovered the uranium
and dismantled the organisation.
Mission accomplished,
you may return to base.
Once again, you've shown great
efficiency on this difficult mission.
REFLECTION IN A DEAD DIAMOND
Mr. Diman?
The guest in 317 has
complained again.
Please be more discreet.
It's already Wednesday.
Don't forget to pay for your week.
It's a time full of promise.
Our products will
help feed the world.
Nuclear energy isn't
just about weaponry, John.
It's about access to modernity.
Electricity for everyone.
We are entering a new era.
Thanks to your work, no one
will ever lack anything again.
We can enjoy everything today.
"Sky is the limit"
has become obsolete.
This is Markus Strand.
He's worth over a million
barrels of oil per day.
He's our top priority.
Get close to him
and protect him as if he were what
you cherish most in the world.
Excuse me.
This car is fitted with two .
50-calibre machine guns.
They're installed in the headlights.
This cigar case becomes a
sight adaptable to your weapon.
This watch is a remote detonator.
This ring allows you to see through
walls thanks to a powerful laser.
But be careful not to leave
it active for too long,
otherwise it will destroy
whatever it's placed against.
I know it's you.
I'm telling you, it's not me!
Do you think I don't know you?
Enough!
I've had enough!
Do you know her?
Do you work for her?
I know nothing.
Even if you don't talk,
I'll know what's in your head.
Did you see her?
What's she like?
Describe her face to me.
Tell me who she is!
I've already told you everything!
You're going to tell
me all your secrets!
Tell me!
You'll be there.
I'll be watching you
when you're with Strand.
I'm the one keeping
an eye on things.
My dress records
everything I decide.
Touch me again
and you're dead.
I'll pass.
You're giving up
rather quickly, my dear.
I want to see.
The bets are placed.
No more bets.
I have a proposal for you.
Of course.
Whenever you like.
Something's wrong.
We're not the only ones
on the Strand job.
I'm not talking millions,
but tens of millions of barrels.
Don't worry.
My resources are limitless.
Someone wants to set a trap for us.
I repeat, code red.
Papillon Nuit, it's Alpha.
Send us reinforcements.
Papillon Nuit, do you copy?
Forget it, we can't rely on them.
You won.
Now you just have to
play with your body.
Mr. Strand, when can
we meet to discuss it?
I'll sort that with your associate.
Smile!
Meet me at the range.
It's a time full of promise.
Soon all our gadgets will
fit on a single phone.
I swear to you,
we're entering a new era.
The binary system offers
infinite possibilities.
Everything is changing!
If John remains binary and keeps
seeing the world in black and white,
good and evil,
man and woman,
technology will change nothing.
I get the feeling he's more
interested in his oil paintings.
These paintings make
my blood run cold.
Something is changing.
We are in danger.
They want to eliminate us.
We can make you an attractive offer.
I'm listening.
I'm waiting for the green
light from my associate,
but I haven't heard from her.
She has been missing for a few days.
To me, we don’t just disappear.
We always leave a trace somewhere.
Do you see?
The concept of death...
Excuse me for a moment.
Yes?
What?
Who did this?
In which bar?
Are you certain it was her?
Was she not masked?
How so?
She needed her hair?
I'll take the winner.
Half.
And you?
Where were you?
Wait.
I'll be right back.
Yes, I'm listening...
Reflection of your
work in a dead eye
How did you find
Markus Strand’s body?
Was he already dead
when you arrived?
I've already told you everything!
Your role was to protect him!
If you no longer like your role,
we'll find another agent.
Mr. Diman.
Please.
Mr. Diman!
Invoice 316
Come on, have fun,
it's our last night.
I can't believe they dropped you,
after the last two successes.
We're all just pawns
in their hands.
Replaceable at will.
You too!
Come on! At least I've got
this gorgeous dress.
It's worth all your diamonds.
I won't let your
death go unpunished.
I like you when you're angry, John.
Now that I'm no longer here,
be careful with Serpentik, though.
You might be next.
Goodbye, my love.
I'll avenge you.
Waiter.
Another Martini.
And a plate of sea urchins.
But there are no more
sea urchins, sir.
I've been waiting for
this moment for so long.
Are you finally going
to tell me who you are?
Take off that mask.
I apologise, sir,
but this will be the last.
Reception has blocked your account.
It's time to make an
appointment with the jewellers,
I'll pay them in diamonds.
Who do they think they are?
I'll grind them to dust!
Take off that mask.
I don't want any more
of your mysteries.
I want it to end.
I want it to be over.
Kiss me.
Good day, Mr. Diman.
NEW ACCIDENT AT
THE FOOTBRIDGE
Body of a man
found in the ravine.
NEW BEACHES IN DANGER
CLIENT OF THE MIRAMARE
FOUND DEAD ON COASTAL PATH
Autopsy of the
body is underway.
Autopsy...
...no sign of struggle.
...poisoned.
She paralyses her victims by pricking
them in the neck with a poisoned ring.
This method resembles
the cobra's kiss,
which immobilises its victims
with a fish before killing them.
Once the opponent is immobilised,
she can use her metal nails,
as sharp as a sabre.
PRECIOUS STONE
TRAFFICKER MURDERED!!
She calls herself Serpentik.
She is our number one priority.
But she is not the only one.
We are already on the trail
of the one who massacred
the IAEA members at
the Orient Palace,
and of the one who poisoned
guests at private beaches
in the name of coastal preservation.
But the most dangerous
are not yet identified.
The one who killed
several art collectors
by referring to famous
paintings is still at large.
We only know that he warns his victims
with a message announcing their death.
And here is the last one,
probably the most dangerous.
Kinetic hypnotises her victims,
who then believe they are in a film.
They lose all sense of reality
until the appearance of the word "fin",
which resounds heavily.
Listen to the music of your death.
You must leave.
You are in danger.
I know.
And I don't need your
government's help.
I know who you are.
Stop playing now.
Come back to see me if you
have another charming partner.
Otherwise, leave me alone.
Did you see her?
What is she like?
If you can still manage to speak,
you tell Strand that he's next.
Describe her face to me.
Yes?
He left this for you.
Him again.
Tell him I'm coming.
This smell intoxicates me.
It disgusts me.
Without it,
humanity would still
smell of the fetid caves.
It's my favourite moment.
Farewell.
Humanity will be rid
of your fetid smell.
Gaze upon your work.
- So it was you who killed him?
- Who?
You know very well
who I'm talking about.
Someone saw you at the crime scene.
It's not me.
Serpentik is behind all this.
But who is Serpentik?
Poisoning is her modus operandi!
Stop with Serpentik.
And her - who decided
to eliminate her?
I've had enough!
She was one of the
best, full of promise.
Was! She's become obsolete.
Serpentik is the future.
- Who is Serpentik?
- No one must know.
And especially not you.
One leak and it's all ruined.
I've had enough of your mysteries.
Forget Serpentik.
Just honour your contract!
Who is Serpentik?
Have you seen her?
What does she look like?
Describe her face.
Have you ever worked with her?
Why all this mystery?
THE SERPENTIK MYSTERY
Who is hiding behind the mask?
Serpentik is just one
mask among so many others.
WHICH ACTRESS IS HIDING
BEHIND SERPENTIK?
Is it the first time a
woman has resisted you?
I...
Do you see a bright
future for Serpentik?
Do you think she'll bring a breathe
of fresh air and a welcome change?
"Operation Serpentik"
will be a success.
Play the game and
everything will be fine.
And don't forget, if it's not you,
someone else will do
the job in your place.
Don't become your
own worst enemy!
NOTHING WILL STOP
SERPENTIK
I WILL NOT ALLOW
THIS TO HAPPEN
Everything was changing
and collapsing around me.
Who was the cause of it?
Them...
...or me?
ATOMIK’S SECRET REVEALED!
AMPHIBIK'S PROJECT IS
DEAD IN THE WATER!
Behind those masks,
I found nothing but chaos.
SOON I WILL KNOW WHO
IS BEHIND SERPENTIK!
And I knew what I would find at the
end of that long road of destruction.
I've dreamt of this
moment for so long.
Do you think I don't know you?
Would you like to know me?
You'd rather know who you are.
To understand the
meaning of your actions.
The world you live in.
You're going to tell
me all your secrets,
before letting this
world rest in peace.
Your fight is only an illusion.
Your world is only an illusion.
THE THOUSAND FACES
OF SERPENTIK
Madam.
I wish to see Mr. Diman.
Mr. Diman is unavailable.
Could you give him
this envelope from me?
Of course.
He is with the police for now.
She was his neighbour.
So, are we releasing him?
Do we keep him under surveillance?
He's completely harmless.
Leave him in peace.
- OK, you can release him.
- Fine.
Mr. Diman, you're free.
It's working!
Everyone wants to know who she is.
Even the foreign press is
talking about Serpentik.
She's going to
knock 'em dead!
Gentlemen, "Operation
Serpentik" will be a success!
But we must keep an eye on Diman.
Why?
He's losing it.
I fear he won't honour the contract.
He could ruin everything
and compromise our strategy!
We must keep him in check.
We must protect her,
she's complained about him again.
Last time, she had
to barricade herself in.
OK, we'll keep him
under observation.
But afterwards,
we'll have to get rid of him.
Yes, I'm already looking
for his replacement.
I have photos, I can
show them to you.
In the meantime,
we must reassure him.
Before the final
confrontation with her.
Cut!
Too much blood!
Sorry, I went too far.
Are you all right?
Did I hurt you?
No, no problem.
Don't move, I'll add
a bit more blood.
You put more "chocolate" in today.
"Chocolate"?
- Ah, chocolate!
- Chocolate.
- Yes, it's excellent.
- Thank you.
Did you see her?
She's not here yet.
Yes, she's in her dressing room,
I only saw her magnificent eyes.
Tell me.
I don't know anything, I told you.
I can only tell you that I have never
put makeup on an actress's eyes.
Everyone to your places!
Ready?
You're furious: you see Serpentik
behind every woman you meet!
You want to find her,
you want to finish her,
and find out who's
hiding behind the mask!
It's driving you mad!
I want you to give it your all, OK?
Affirmative, boss.
Camera!
ACTION!!!
Did you see her?
I know it was you.
You're going to tell
me all your secrets.
- Do you think I don't know you?
- I don't know anything!
- Where is she hiding?
- I've already told you everything!
I've never seen her!
Do you know her?
Do you work for her?
- Answer me!
- I don't know her!
Tell me who she is!
It's not me!
You're going to tell me all
your secrets! Where is she?
I don't know her!
Enough!
I've had enough!
I've lost her.
Does anyone have
visual contact with her?
Yes, she just passed the bus stop.
She took the path that
leads up to the town.
She went through the pinewood.
- I've lost her again.
- I've found her hideout.
She was on the path
that overlooks the sea.
Everyone hold position,
I'm coming.
She went into her lair.
She's just gone past!
She isn't alone.
Another one!
How many are there?
I counted five.
No, there's only one!
She's changing to try to escape us.
I want her alive!
We'll finish her off.
On three, go.
One, two, three!
They're worthless.
Fake.
That's not possible!
- Serpentik...
- I'm sorry, Mr. Diman...
...but you must vacate your room.
POISONED
...
BY THE SEA
...swimming prohibited
Mr. Diman, a lady left
this for you.
What have you done to me?
I've been dreaming of
this moment for so long.
You have to wait a bit
because I still need you.
Take off this mask.
You're like me,
you have many faces.
I've had enough of your mysteries!
I want it to end.
You want to put an end to it while
you think the future is bright.
You're becoming less binary
than the language
of progress that gives you so much hope.
Kiss me.
I'll finish it.
I am not your worst enemy.
I don't want you to die.
Not now.
"Operation Serpentik" is a failure.
It's over for you.
But "John" must carry on.
Hello?
Yes?
Don't move.
You've fainted.
You need to rest.
Who's the woman
who just left?
She's the one who
settled your bills.
You can stay at the hotel
until you're back on your feet.
Mr. Diman, you mustn't
get up so quickly!
I'm all right!
I don't need you!
I've been dreaming of
this moment for so long.
Your favourite drink.
This house belonged to
my husband when you came.
Your husband?
Markus Strand?
No, he rented it for
Operation Serpentik.
Do you know her?
A VERY SPECIAL AGENT
I've changed.
I'm not the same any more.
I don't think you've
changed that much.
I'll get you!
I know it's you!
TELL ME ALL
YOUR SECRETS!
Remove the mask!
Enough!
Why didn't you come sooner?
My dream was chaos.
And in the end, you
were my worst nightmare.
John, who fights for
the good of humanity,
was far more effective than
I was at destroying the world.
REFLECTION IN A
DEAD DIAMOND